

# IVAN MATEJČIĆ

software developer

- +385 98 9406 500
- ivanmatejcic1@gmail.com
- ivan-matejcic.netlify.app
- Ulica Kralja Zvonimira 19, 51260 Crikvenica, Hrvatska

### **About Me**

I am a 5th-year graduate student of computer science at the University of Rijeka. I completed elementary education at Vladimir Nazor Elementary School in Crikvenica, and secondary education at Pazinski Kolegij-classical gymnasium with public authority, Pazin. Motivated worker with proven abilities in quality, reliable work, and experience in relevant modern web technologies (Angular, .NET,...). My goal is continuous learning, constant improvement of my skills, and education in various areas of computer science.

## **Work Experience**

October 2022 - Present GDi | Rijeka

#### **Full Stack Software Developer**

- Began working shortly after internship
- Full-stack software developer position
- Work on a large-scale geo-informational system
- Developing both backend (REST API) and frontend solutions
- Implementing solutions for clients using .NET, TypeScript, Angular
- Working in a communicative, team environment
- Independent, passionate, reliable work
- Providing solutions, problem-solving
- .NET, Angular, Azure

May 2022 - September 2022

Own.Solutions | Rijeka

## Internship

- 3 month internship
- Started after a successful project campaign as a group effort
- As a result (1st place), awarded with financial compensation
- Implementing internal solutions in Python
- Using Google API's to develop scripts and services which expanded the company's existing systems, creating additional values

## **Digital skills**

- C# (.NET, Unity)
- TypeScript (Angular),
- Python (Django)
- SQL (SQL Server, MySQL, Postgres, MariaDB)
- NoSQL, MongoDB, Firebase, Docker,
- Blender, Adobe tools (Photoshop, Illustrator, Audition)
- WordPress,
- Other: Git, Heroku, Bootstrap
- OS: Linux (Ubuntu), Windows, Mac OS

## Language skills

- Mother language
  - Croatian
- Other languages
  - English

## **Education**

#### **Graduate**

Fakultet Informatike i Digitalnih Tehnologija

Oct 2022 - Current

#### **Undergraduate**

Fakultet Informatike i Digitalnih Tehnologija

Oct 2019 - Sep 2022

High School Graduate
Pazinski Kolegij

Sep 2015 - Jun 2019